Guide to the Nine Mile Run Greenway Project Records, 1945-2005 AIS.2006.19A
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Reference Material, 1951-2001; VIII.
  - Bound Publications, 1951-2001; 3.
    - "Phase III Environmental Site Assessment Nine Mile Run Slag Area" By: Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh, June 1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Workshops, 1997-2001; IX.
  This series contains workshop material created during the Nine Mile Run Greenway project, and is divided into three subseries by the name of the individual programs: Ample Opportunity I, Ample Opportunity II, and Ample Opportunity III. The workshops included panel discussions by experts in specific areas such as history, public policy, stream remediation, ecology and brownfields. The public was invited to attend these discussions which were followed by opportunities for small group discussions and gathering of information from attendees. This interaction facilitated the collection of oral histories and documents related to the historical usage of the Nine Mile Run watershed region.
  - Ample Opportunity I: Community Dialogue, January 1997-December 1997; 1.
    This subseries contains material relating to Ample Opportunity I: Community Dialogue. Ample Opportunity I lasted from January 1997 to December 1997 and consisted of four workshops and a greenway tour.
    - Workshop I: History, Context, and Public Policy, July 2, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Workshop II: Stream Remediation, July 19, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Workshop III: Slag, Soil, Plants, and Wildlife or Community and Ecology, August 2, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Workshop IV: Sustainable Open Space, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Non-workshop material, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Greenway tours, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Water Tech Committee, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Final Report, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Ample Opportunity II: Brownfield Intervention, January 1998-December 1998; 2.
    This subseries contains material relating to Ample Opportunity II: Brownfield Intervention. Ample Opportunity II lasted from January 1998 to December 1998 and created material pertaining the following topics: Bioblitz, Clean-up day, Community meetings, storm water management/Charette project, and summary material.
    - Bioblitz, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Clean-up Day, May 9, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Community Meetings, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Storm Water Management/Charette Project, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 25-27)
    - Summary Material, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Ample Opportunity III: The Transformation, January 1999-January 2001; 3.
    This subseries contains material relating to Ample Opportunity III: The Transformation. Ample Opportunity III lasted from January 1999 to January 2001.
    - Grant Planning, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Audio-Visual Material, 1996-1999; X.
  This series contains audio-visual material that was created by the Nine Mile Run Greenway project. The types of media present in this series include photographs, photographic negatives, slides, VHS tapes, videocassette tapes, audio tapes, hard drives, discs (CD-ROM), and floppy disks.
  - Photographs, 1996-1998; 1.
    This subseries contains 15 folders of photographic material that document the Nine Mile Run Greenway Project between 1996-1999, and are broken down into four main topics: Tours and Events; Slag, Vegetation, Wildlife, Soil Testing; Stream, Pipes, Aquatic Organisms, Water Testing, Riparian, Erosion, Wetlands; and Trailer, History, 3D Model, Car Burning, Old Brownsfield Road, Mouth of River, Duck Hollow. This organization is reflective of the original structure that was found when the items were donated (4 binders with corresponding titles).
    - Binder I: "Tours and Events", 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 30-33)
    - Binder II: "Slag, Vegetation, Wildlife, Soil Testing", c1998 (Box 7, Folder 1-4)
    - Binder III: "Stream, Pipes, Aquatic Organisms, Water Testing, Riparian, Erosion, Wetlands", c1998 (Box 7, Folder 5-7)
    - Binder IV: "Trailer, History, 3D Model, Car Burning, Old Brownsfield Road, Mouth of River, Duck Hollow", c1998 (Box 7, Folder 8-10)
    - Loose photographs, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Slides, c1996-1999; 2.
    This subseries contains projection slides that were used to both document the Nine Mile Run Project and for programs. This organization is reflective of the original structure that was found when the items were donated; there were multiple partitioned binders with each section titled one of the ten topics. These items are predominately undated.
    - Binder I: "3D Model, Graphics, Misc." (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
    - Binder II: "EPA Test Pits, Greenhouse' [slides and prints] (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Binder III: "Art" (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
    - Binder IV: "Education" (Box 7, Folder 17-18)
    - Binder IV: "Education" (con't) (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Binder V: "Event Tours", 1999 (Box 8, Folder 3-6)
    - Binder VI: "History, Land, Slag" (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
    - Binder VII: "Participant Resumes and Slides", 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
    - Binder VIII: "Slag, Vegetation, Wildlife, Soil Testing" (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
    - Binder IX: "Streams" (Box 8, Folder 14-16)
    - Binder X: "Wood Street Gallery" (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
  - Camcorder Tapes, 1990-1999; 3.
    This subseries contains 86 camcorder tapes that document the Nine Mile Run Greenway Project. Titles given here reflect the labeling on the original containers.
    - "Bioblitz", 1998 (Box 9, Item 1)
    - "Bioblitz Trail", Undated (Box 9, Item 2)
    - "Children's Museum no. 1", Undated (Box 9, Item 3)
    - "Children's Museum no. 2", Undated (Box 9, Item 4)
    - "Children's Museum Site Tour", November 1997 (Box 9, Item 5)
    - "City of Pittsburgh GIS Files", Undated (Box 9, Item 6)
    - "Claire Staples Oral Histories", July 14, 1997 (Box 9, Item 7)
    - "County GIS Files", Undated (Box 9, Item 8)
    - "DCNR Community Meeting", June 1, 1998 (Box 9, Item 9)
    - "DCNR Community Meeting", June 1, 1998 (Box 9, Item 10)
    - "DCNR no. 1", 1998 (Box 9, Item 11)
    - "DCNR no. 2", Undated (Box 9, Item 12)
    - "Dixon/Montessori", Undated (Box 9, Item 13)
    - "Doug Lambert Walk from Duck Hollow Showing Nine Mile Run Flowing into a Sewer", August 4, 1997 (Box 9, Item 14)
    - "Duck Hollow Interview with Eileen Bell", November 21, 1996 (Box 9, Item 15)
    - "Environmental Art Discussion Tape no. 1", Undated (Box 9, Item 16)
    - "Eugene Levy Oral History", July 10, 1997 (Box 9, Item 17)
    - "History, Context, Public Policy, Public Dialogues", July 2, 1997 (Box 9, Item 18)
    - "History, Context, Public Policy, Public Dialogues", July 2, 1997 (Box 9, Item 19)
    - "Homewood Montessori: Lois and Reiko's Visit Nine Mile Run AAA Ideas", Undated (Box 9, Item 20)
    - "Joe Robinson", September 16, 1996 (Box 9, Item 21)
    - "Joel Tarr Interview", Undated (Box 9, Item 22)
    - "John Buck Soil/Slag Tour", August 2, 1997 (Box 9, Item 23)
    - "John Oyler's Talk and First Half of Soil/Slag Discussion", August 2, 1997 (Box 9, Item 24)
    - "John Oyler's Talk and Second Half of Soil/Slag Discussion", August 2, 1997 (Box 9, Item 25)
    - "Minadeo Field Trip, Montessori, and Minadeo", April 7, 1998-June 10, 1998 (Box 9, Item 26)
    - "Montessori Sumie", October 6, 1999 (Box 9, Item 27)
    - "Nine Mile Run Conference on History/Context at the Irish Center", July 2, 1997 (Box 9, Item 28)
    - "Nine Mile Run Conference on Public Policy at the Irish Center", July 2, 1997 (Box 9, Item 29)
    - "Nine Mile Run DCNR Stream Walk", Undated (Box 9, Item 30)
    - "Nine Mile Run Development Public Hearing at St. Edmund's Academy in Squirrel Hill no. 1 of 3", March 27, 1997 (Box 9, Item 31)
    - "Nine Mile Run Development Public Hearing at St. Edmund's Academy in Squirrel Hill no. 2 of 3", March 27, 1997 (Box 9, Item 32)
    - "Nine Mile Run Development Public Hearing no. 3 of 3", March 27, 1997 (Box 9, Item 33)
    - "Nine Mile Run Duck Hollow Gathering: John Buck Soil/Slag Walk, John Oyler Presentation at Swisshelm Park Community Center", August 2, 1997 (Box 9, Item 34)
    - "Nine Mile Run Frick Evironment Opening Remarks", October 23, 1997 (Box 9, Item 35)
    - "Nine Mile Run Frick Environmental Table no. 1", October 23, 1997 (Box 9, Item 36)
    - "Nine Mile Run Frick Environmental Table no. 2", October 23, 1997 (Box 9, Item 37)
    - "Nine Mile Run Frick Environmental Table no. 3", October 23, 1997 (Box 9, Item 38)
    - "Nine Mile Run Habitat-Vegetation", August 2, 1997 (Box 9, Item 39)
    - "Nine Mile Run History Video: Titles/Graphics", Undated (Box 9, Item 40)
    - "Nine Mile Run Main Disc", Undated (Box 9, Item 41)
    - "Nine Mile Run Montessori School Tour", Undated (Box 9, Item 42)
    - "Nine Mile Run Oral History Master Rough Edit", Undated (Box 9, Item 43)
    - "Nine Mile Run Panel Discussion", July 19, 1997 (Box 9, Item 44)
    - "Nine Mile Run Public Access", August 2, 1997 (Box 9, Item 45)
    - "Nine Mile Run Regulation and Reality", July 19, 1997 (Box 9, Item 46)
    - "Nine Mile Run Slag", August 2, 1997 (Box 9, Item 47)
    - "Nine Mile Run Sound Experiment", Undated (Box 9, Item 48)
    - "Nine Mile Run Storm Test Site no. 4", May 26, 199- (Box 9, Item 49)
    - "Nine Mile Run Stream Banks and Flood Plains", July 19, 1997 (Box 9, Item 50)
    - "Nine Mile Run Stream Ecology", July 19, 1997 (Box 9, Item 51)
    - "Nine Mile Run Upper Tour no. 4", Undated (Box 9, Item 52)
    - "Nine Mile Run URA City", December 13, 1990 (Box 9, Item 53)
    - Unlabeled, Undated (Box 9, Item 54)
    - Unlabeled, Undated (Box 9, Item 55)
    - "Presentation of Saturday Charette One of Two", October 16, 199- (Box 9, Item 56)
    - "Presentation of Saturday Charette Two of Two", October 16, 199- (Box 9, Item 57)
    - "R. Gangawere", Undated (Box 9, Item 58)
    - "RMI Intro", Undated (Box 9, Item 59)
    - "Robert Gangawere Oral history", July 21, 1997 (Box 9, Item 60)
    - "Slag Group no. 1 Marchall Ebert Interview", January 1, 1997 (Box 9, Item 61)
    - "Slag Heap with Chris Mark: Water on Path, Winter Scope", Undated (Box 9, Item 62)
    - "Squirrel Hill Coalition Open Space Meeting at the Rehab Center no. 1", September 10, 1997 (Box 9, Item 63)
    - "Squirrel Hill Coalition Open Space Meeting at the Rehab Center no. 2", September 10, 1997 (Box 9, Item 64)
    - "Stream (Damaged)", Undated (Box 10, Item 1)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop, Ann Riley (Close-Up) and Half Group Discussion", July 19, 1997 (Box 10, Item 2)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop, Ann Riley (Wide) and 20 mn. Group Discussion", July 19, 1997 (Box 10, Item 3)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop, Group Discussion and John Schrombert Part 2", Undated (Box 10, Item 4)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop, John Schrombeck Upstream Tour", July 19, 1997 (Box 10, Item 5)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop, Local Experts Close-Ups", July 19, 1997 (Box 10, Item 6)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop, Local Experts Wide Shots", July 19, 1997 (Box 10, Item 7)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop, Stream Eco and Urb Pro, Stream Banks and Flood", July 19, 1997 (Box 10, Item 8)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop, Stream Walk with Tim", July 19, 1997 (Box 10, Item 9)
    - "Swisshelm Park Community Center", April 3, 1997 (Box 10, Item 10)
    - "Swisshelm Park Community Meeting no. 2", April 2, 1997 (Box 10, Item 11)
    - "Swisshelm Park Community Meeting no. 3", April 2, 1997 (Box 10, Item 12)
    - "Tim and Reiko", September 10, 199- (Box 10, Item 13)
    - "Vegetation and Habitat Environment Education Roundtable", August 2, 1997 (Box 10, Item 14)
    - "Walk about Trail Focus", August 25, 1997 (Box 10, Item 15)
    - "Wood Street Community Workshop no. 1", Undated (Box 10, Item 16)
    - "Wood Street Community Workshop no. 2", Undated (Box 10, Item 17)
    - "Wood Street Community Workshop no. 3", Undated (Box 10, Item 18)
    - "Wood Street Community Workshop no. 4", Undated (Box 10, Item 19)
    - "Wood Street Community Workshop no. 5", Undated (Box 10, Item 20)
    - "Wood Street Community Workshop no. 6", Undated (Box 10, Item 21)
    - "Wood Street Community Workshop no. 7", Undated (Box 10, Item 22)
  - Audio Tapes, 4.
    This subseries contains 59 audio-cassette tapes. Titles given here reflect the labeling on the original containers.
    - "Andrew/Nine Mile Run", 1997 (Box 11, Item 1)
    - "Andrew/Nine Mile Run", 1997 (Box 11, Item 2)
    - "Ann Riley Radio Interview" (Box 11, Item 3)
    - "BH Opening, Nine Mile Run" (Box 11, Item 4)
    - "Chris Craychee(?)", 1998 (Box 11, Item 5)
    - "Dickson, Montessori Visiting Fall 1998 KDKA News" (Box 11, Item 6)
    - "Doug", 1998 (Box 11, Item 7)
    - "Edgewood Final Presentation Quesions and Responses" (Box 11, Item 8)
    - "Eilleen Bell Cont./Joe Robinson Interview (Box 11, Item 9)
    - "Eilleen Bell Duck Hollow Rep.", 1996 (Box 11, Item 10)
    - "Environmental Art Discussion tape no. 3" (Box 11, Item 11)
    - "History, Policy, and Context Workshop", 1997 (Box 11, Item 12)
    - "History, Policy, and Context Workshop", 1997 (Box 11, Item 13)
    - "Malcolm Mile", 1999 (Box 11, Item 14)
    - "Nine MIle Run Eugene Levy Oral History", 1997 (Box 11, Item 15)
    - "Nine Mile Run Frick Enivronmental Center Opening/Closing Remarks", 1997 (Box 11, Item 16)
    - "Nine Mile Run Frick Environmental Center table no. 1" (Box 11, Item 17)
    - "Nine Mile Run Frick Environmental Center table no. 3" (Box 11, Item 18)
    - "Nine Mile Run Habitat and Vegetation Swisshelm Park Community Center", 1997 (Box 11, Item 19)
    - "Nine Mile Run Main Discussion Swisshelm Park Community Center", 1997 (Box 11, Item 20)
    - "Nine Mile Run Public Access Swisshelm Park Community Center", 1997 (Box 11, Item 21)
    - Not labeled (Box 11, Item 22)
    - Not labeled (Box 11, Item 23)
    - Not labeled (Box 11, Item 24)
    - Not labeled (Box 11, Item 25)
    - "Paula Gun Allen" (Box 11, Item 26)
    - "Rich", 1998 (Box 11, Item 27)
    - "RMI Discussion Hunter" (Box 11, Item 28)
    - "RMI Discussion Original" (Box 11, Item 29)
    - "RMI Discussion Policy Final" (Box 11, Item 30)
    - "RMI Discussion Sterrett Beverly and Dan" (Box 11, Item 31)
    - "RMI Final Presentation 1", 1998 (Box 11, Item 32)
    - "RMI Final Presentation 2", 1998 (Box 11, Item 33)
    - "RMI Final Presentation Original" (Box 11, Item 34)
    - "Robert Gangawere Oral History", 1997 (Box 11, Item 35)
    - "S. Clare Staples" (Box 11, Item 36)
    - "Slag, Soil, Habitat", 1997 (Box 11, Item 37)
    - "Soil, Slag, Habitat", 1997 (Box 11, Item 38)
    - "Soil, Slag, Habitat Advisory Meeting", 1997 (Box 11, Item 39)
    - "Soil, Slag, Habitat Meeting", 1997 (Box 11, Item 40)
    - "Stream" (Box 11, Item 41)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop Ann Riley", 1997 (Box 11, Item 42)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop Group Discussion Stream Banks and Flood Plains", 1997 (Box 11, Item 43)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop Group Discussion Stream Ecology", 1997 (Box 11, Item 44)
    - "Stream Remediation Workshop Group Discussion, Stream Banks, and Flood Plains", 1997 (Box 11, Item 45)
    - "Stream RemediationWorkshop Local Extent Introduction of Approaches", 1997 (Box 11, Item 46)
    - "Stream RemediationWorkshop, Stream Banks, a Flood Plain, and Regulation and Reality", 1997 (Box 11, Item 47)
    - "Swisshelm Park Meeting", 1997 (Box 11, Item 48)
    - "Tape Four Policy", 1998 (Box 11, Item 49)
    - "Tape One" (Box 11, Item 50)
    - "Tape One" (Box 11, Item 51)
    - "Tape Two" (Box 11, Item 52)
    - "Tape Three" (Box 11, Item 53)
    - "Task Force Squirrel Hill Coalition", 1997 (Box 11, Item 54)
    - "UDA Public Meeting", 1997 (Box 11, Item 55)
    - "Water Tech no. 3", 1997 (Box 11, Item 56)
    - "Water Tech", 1997 (Box 11, Item 57)
    - "Water Tech", 1997 (Box 11, Item 58)
    - "Western Pennsylvania Town Meeting", 1998 (Box 11, Item 59)
  - Electronic Media, 5.
    This subseries consists of two CD's, 37 computer discs, and 68 zip discs. Titles given here reflect the labeling on the original containers.
    - CD-Rom, 1999-2000
      - Disc – "Frick Old Aerials, City Park Aerials, Frick historical Plan, Old Frick Aerial PSD, and Where is this movie", 1999 (Box 11, Item 60)
      - Disc – "Transforming Nine Mile Run", 2000 (Box 11, Item 61)
    - Floppy Disks, c1996-2000
      - "ACAD Images" (Box 11, Item 62)
      - "ACAD Images" (Box 11, Item 63)
      - "Audrey Aubrecht Frick Environmental Class" (Box 11, Item 64)
      - "Audrey Aubrecht Nature Walk Booklet" (Box 11, Item 65)
      - "Beck Beveridge Ramsey Elementary 3rd Grade AIU Module" (Box 11, Item 66)
      - "Bird List, Black, Floyd, CM Data for Frick Park and Environs" (Box 11, Item 67)
      - "Flow Data - Excel" (Box 11, Item 68)
      - "Hunter Park" (Box 11, Item 69)
      - "Met Museum Letter", 1997 (Box 11, Item 70)
      - "Nine Bugs" (Box 11, Item 71)
      - "Nine Mile Run" (Box 11, Item 72)
      - "Nine Mile Run Business Plan" (Box 11, Item 73)
      - "Nine Mile Run Charette Documents produced", 1998 (Box 11, Item 74)
      - "Nine Mile Run GIS Disk 1 of 2" (Box 11, Item 75)
      - "Nine Mile Run GIS Disk 2 of 2" (Box 11, Item 76)
      - "Nine Mile Run Heather Bellante gr. 4 Spring Hill" (Box 11, Item 77)
      - "Nine Mile Run John Meldon" (Box 11, Item 78)
      - Not Labeled (Box 11, Item 79)
      - Not Labeled (Box 11, Item 80)
      - Not Labeled (Box 11, Item 81)
      - Not Labeled (Box 11, Item 82)
      - Not Labeled (Box 11, Item 83)
      - Not Labeled (Box 11, Item 84)
      - Not Labeled (Box 11, Item 85)
      - Not Labeled (Box 11, Item 86)
      - "Orsanco/milepnt 4.3" (Box 11, Item 87)
      - "Reiko" (Box 11, Item 88)
      - "RMI" (Box 11, Item 89)
      - "Rose Reilly, Herb, Tim, Reiko" (Box 11, Item 90)
      - "Signs and Fonts T. Collins" (Box 11, Item 91)
      - "Sound Class P.R." (Box 11, Item 92)
      - "Sterrett.dxf" (Box 11, Item 93)
      - "Tabs" (Box 11, Item 94)
      - "Timothy Collins Sheraton Hotel 2817" (Box 11, Item 95)
      - "Peggy's Transect no. 1 Lotus 1-2-3" (Box 11, Item 96)
      - "Transect 2" (Box 11, Item 97)
      - "Wetlands Treatment Database" (Box 11, Item 98)
    - Zip Disks, c1996-2000
      - "1: Panorama, 18: Sustainable Open Space, 19: Forest Photos" (Box 12, Item 1)
      - "2: Aerial Photograph, 3: Map, 4: Trailer, 5: Philosophy, 13: Hop Tree" (Box 12, Item 2)
      - "5, 6: Graphs, 7: Biblio" (Box 12, Item 3)
      - "10: Water/Culvert, 11: Stream Reclamation, 12: Pittsburgh Map, 9: History in Context" (Box 12, Item 4)
      - "14: Background Picture, 16: Community Ecology" (Box 12, Item 5)
      - "15: Community Ecology Speaker, 17: 3-D Model, 6: Alt. Scene and Ecology "Progress", 7: History Olmsted, 8: History" (Box 12, Item 6)
      - "1200 DPI A. Carngeie R. Serra" (Box 12, Item 7)
      - "1200 DPI Carngeie Sculpture 500 DPI" (Box 12, Item 8)
      - "A. G. Trimble" (Box 12, Item 9)
      - "Aerial Photos Stream Rising Series" (Box 12, Item 10)
      - "Birds" (Box 12, Item 11)
      - "Bird Painting, Field Trip 1998, Dickson" (Box 12, Item 12)
      - "Carnegie Mellon" (Box 12, Item 13)
      - "Children's Drawings" (Box 12, Item 14)
      - "Charlotte GIS" (Box 12, Item 15)
      - "Charette Back-up Suzy Final" (Box 12, Item 16)
      - "Chayora" (Box 12, Item 17)
      - "Chuck Tague Girl Scout Summer Workshop" (Box 12, Item 18)
      - "Current Website Travel Packet" (Box 12, Item 19)
      - "DCNR Final", 1998 (Box 12, Item 20)
      - "ED Other Images MI-8 Final Tim Edits 12/18" (Box 12, Item 21)
      - "Education Gallery, Heinz, Reiko Tour" (Box 12, Item 22)
      - "Fall 1999 Class Visit (Box 12, Item 23)
      - "Fall 1999 Class Visit 2" (Box 12, Item 24)
      - "Fall 1999 Class Visit 3" (Box 12, Item 25)
      - "Final Project Sand Box" (Box 12, Item 26)
      - "Finished Photos 1938 02.13.01" (Box 12, Item 27)
      - "History" (Box 12, Item 28)
      - "History Images" (Box 12, Item 29)
      - "IBM Sign Disk" (Box 12, Item 30)
      - "IBM Talk Multi-Image Scans" (Box 12, Item 31)
      - "Images M-1 Urban Watershed" (Box 12, Item 32)
      - "JWS AAA Children's Museum" (Box 12, Item 33)
      - "Kirk's Images" (Box 12, Item 34)
      - "Mac Tranfers" (Box 12, Item 35)
      - "Minudeo" (Box 12, Item 36)
      - "Montessorri 1" (Box 12, Item 37)
      - "Montessori 2" (Box 12, Item 38)
      - "New Images, Book Images" (Box 12, Item 39)
      - "New Images 2" (Box 12, Item 40)
      - "New Images 3" (Box 12, Item 41)
      - "Nine Mile Run" (Box 12, Item 42)
      - "Nine Mile Run Archive and Back-ups" (Box 12, Item 43)
      - "Nine Mile Run Greenway Project" (Box 12, Item 44)
      - "Nine Mile Run Wood Street Announce" (Box 12, Item 45)
      - Not Labeled (Box 12, Item 46)
      - "Number 3: Stream, number 4: Community and Ecology" (Box 12, Item 47)
      - "Other ED Images M2-B (Box 12, Item 48)
      - "Panoramic" (Box 12, Item 49)
      - "Poster Suk/Brun" (Box 12, Item 50)
      - "Reiko Brownfield Life" (Box 12, Item 51)
      - "Reiko Powerpoint Manhattan Beach" (Box 12, Item 52)
      - "Reiko Slides" (Box 12, Item 53)
      - "Reiko Travel" (Box 12, Item 54)
      - "Rescan Slides 300 DPI" (Box 12, Item 55)
      - "RMI/Hunter Park" (Box 12, Item 56)
      - "RMI Sites" (Box 12, Item 57)
      - "Slide Images Picture Format" (Box 12, Item 58)
      - "Small Brewhouse Exhibition Pieces" (Box 12, Item 59)
      - "Suzy Meyer" (Box 12, Item 60)
      - "Suzy Meyer Enhanced Tiff" (Box 12, Item 61)
      - "Tim: Riverbank Export Anal." (Box 12, Item 62)
      - "Tim Collins SFCI Parts 1 and 2" (Box 12, Item 63)
      - "Tim Water/Hist Images" (Box 12, Item 64)
      - "Tim's Roadshow" (Box 12, Item 65)
      - "Water Video" (Box 12, Item 66)
      - "Wood Street Poster" (Box 12, Item 67)
      - "Workshop Digital Pictures Workshop 2" (Box 12, Item 68)
  - VHS, 1996-c2000; 6.
    This subseries contains 44 VHS tapes that document the Nine Mile Run Greenway Project. Titles given here reflect the labeling on the original containers.
    - "A Walk in Slag", April 19, 1997 (Box 13, Item 1)
    - "Akagi Nature Park", Undated (Box 13, Item 2)
    - "Ample Opportunity", June-August 1997 (Box 13, Item 3)
    - "Ample Opportunity", June 1997 (Box 13, Item 4)
    - "Ample Opportunity", July 19, 1997 (Box 13, Item 5)
    - "Andropogon", Undated (Box 13, Item 6)
    - "Charette no. 2", Undated (Box 13, Item 7)
    - "CSO (Combined Sewer Overflow) Video", Undated (Box 13, Item 8)
    - "Dickson Montessori Visit", Fall 1998 (Box 13, Item 9)
    - "Dry Slag Walk", Undated (Box 13, Item 10)
    - "Evaluating Nine Mile Run Education Program", Undated (Box 13, Item 11)
    - "Fecal Fountain", Undated (Box 13, Item 12)
    - "Fly Up Mon", July 27, 1999 (Box 13, Item 13)
    - "Fly Up Mon Master", July 2, 1999 (Box 13, Item 14)
    - "Fridg Act", Undated (Box 13, Item 15)
    - "Helicopter Fly Up: Monongahela River and Nine Mile Run", 1999 (Box 14, Item 1)
    - "KDKA News", January 21, 1999 (Box 14, Item 2)
    - "Land Walk Nine Mile Run", Undated (Box 14, Item 3)
    - "Lois and Reiko's Visit to Homewood Montessori: AAA Ideas" (Box 14, Item 4)
    - "Mapping the Heap Video Documentation", 1997 (Box 14, Item 5)
    - "Materials", Undated (Box 14, Item 6)
    - "Nine Mile Run Education Fragments (Cakeshia, Questions, and Musi)", Undated (Box 14, Item 7)
    - "Nine Mile Run Education Fragments (Transfer, Cakeshia)", Undated (Box 14, Item 8)
    - "Nine Mile Run History Project Final Cut", April 5, 1999 (Box 14, Item 9)
    - "Nine Mile Run Meeting", December 15, 1995 (Box 14, Item 10)
    - "Nine MIle Run Quadruple Exhibit Copy Water Too Loud", Undated (Box 14, Item 11)
    - "Nine Mile Run Tour", September 6, 1996 (Box 14, Item 12)
    - "Nine Mile Run Walk 2", May 17, 1997 (Box 14, Item 13)
    - "Nine Mile Run Wood Street Community Workshop", Undated (Box 14, Item 14)